Howard Ship Yards and Dock Company mss., 1810-1967 LMC 2278
Lilly Library
- Bound Volumes
  - HSY & DC Stock ledger, 1927, July 19 - 1928, September 5 (Bound 37, Bound 232)
  - HSY & DC Stock ledger, 1927, July 19 - 1931
  - HSY & DC Stock ledger, 1927, July 19 - 1941, January 17 (Bound 51)
  - American Rivers Ship Building Co. Stock ledger`, 1903, June 1 - 1904, November 5
  - American Rivers Ship Building Co. Minutes and articles of incorporation, 1902, November 15 - 1903, December 3
  - Ford Plate Glass Co. Stock ledger, 1877, February 3 - 1889, January 19 (Bound 122)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1839, April 7 - 1847, February 22 (Bound 132)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1857, August 22 - 1859, September 17 (Bound 127)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1859, September 24 - 1863, January 17 (Bound 133)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1863, January 17 - 1865, June 24 (Bound 126)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1873, March 15 - 1875, May 15 (Bound 116)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1875, June 5 - 1877, December 15 (Bound 96)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1877, December 22 - 1879, September 6 (Bound 93)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1879, September 13 - 1881, March 26 (Bound 92)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1881, April 2 - 1882, August 5 (Bound 91)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1882, August 12 - 1884, March 29 (Bound 94)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1888, May 12 - 1890, June 21 (Bound 113)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1890, June 28 - 1892, May 28 (Bound 95)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1892, June 4 - 1894, September 29 (Bound 114)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1894, October 6 - 1897, June 19 (Bound 118)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1897, June 26 - 1899, March 18 (Bound 115)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1899, March 25 - 1901, May 18 (Bound 117)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1901, May 25 - 1903, July 3 (Bound 90)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1903, July 10 - 1905, March 31 (Bound 203)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1909, November 5 - 1912, February 9 (Bound 200)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1912, February 16 - 1914, October 2 (Bound 201)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1914, July 10 - 1917, May 2 (Bound 105)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1917, June 1 - 1920, April 16 (Bound 106)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1920, April 23 - 1921, March 25 (Bound 131)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1921, April 1 - 1924, July 18 (Bound 202)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1924, July 25 - 1926, July 2 (Bound 199)
  - HSY & DC Time book, 1939, May 26 - 1940, December 6 (Bound 169)
  - Ford Plate Glass Co. Time Book, 1879, April 26 - 1880, February 28 (Bound 130)
  - Ohio Falls Street Railway Co. Time book, 1889, June 10 - 1892, September 17 (Bound 28)
  - Time book for specific boats, 1929, November 1 - 1930, July 26 (Bound 16)
  - HSY & DC Trial balance, 1903-1911 (Bound 168)
  - HSY & DC Trial balance, 1929, January - 1933, November (Bound 141)
  - Mississippi Valley Marine Railway & Dock Co. Trial balance, 1906, December - 1913, November (Bound 135)
  - Mound City Branch - Trial balance, 1913, December - 1918, June (Bound 140)
  - Paducah Marine Railway Co. Trial balance, 1906, December - 1913, September (Bound 128)
  - Paducah Branch - Trial balance, 1913, October - 1918, June (Bound 167)
  - Bradstreet's Commercial Reports, Vol. 37, 1875, July 1
  - Bradstreet's Commercial Reports, Vol. 60, 1883, January
- Miscellaneous (Box 77)